A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Politics - New York City Office, Series J.1 FA345
Rockefeller Archive Center
- National Political Campaigns, 1956-1968; 2; 19 Document Box(es)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - McAniff, Mary (Box 27, Folder 0220A)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Menard, Mary Elizabeth (Box 27, Folder 221)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Merne, Arlene Susan (Box 27, Folder 222)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Mitchell, Donna R. (Box 27, Folder 223)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Molitor, Graham (Box 27, Folder 224)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Moore, Jonathan (Box 27, Folder 225)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Morton-Smith, Adrienne (Box 27, Folder 226)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Murphy, Anne (Box 27, Folder 227)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Nathan, Richard (Box 27, Folder 228)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Nicoson, William Jarvie (Box 27, Folder 229)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Oliver, Sandra (Box 27, Folder 230)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Paleologas, Andrea (Box 27, Folder 231)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Persico, Joe (Box 27, Folder 232)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Plummer, Martha (Box 27, Folder 233)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Prince, Horace O'Dare (Box 27, Folder 234)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Quitter, John (Box 27, Folder 235)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Reardon, Kathleen A. (Box 27, Folder 236)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Rice, Helen (Box 27, Folder 237)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Rodmon, Peter (Box 27, Folder 238)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Roes, Audrey (Box 27, Folder 239)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Russell, Marilyn (Box 27, Folder 240)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Sabin, Sharon (Box 27, Folder 241)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Sanchez, Brenda (Box 27, Folder 242)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Sayre, Linda (Box 27, Folder 243)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Seiden, Dena Jill (Box 27, Folder 244)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Stapper, Antoinette (Box 27, Folder 245)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Steele, Susan (Box 27, Folder 246)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Stewart, Katherine (Box 27, Folder 247)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Tenney, Pamela M. (Box 27, Folder 248)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Von Hirsh, Andrew (Box 27, Folder 249)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Wanless, James (Box 27, Folder 250)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Wanless, Karin S. (Box 27, Folder 251)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Ware, Linda R. (Box 27, Folder 252)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Watters, Linda Anne (Box 28, Folder 253)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Watts, William (Box 28, Folder 254)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Wesley, Betty (Box 28, Folder 255)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Weston, Richard (Box 28, Folder 256)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Files - Wolf, Mark L. (Box 28, Folder 257)
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Rockefeller for President - Staff Lists (Box 28, Folder 258)
    DNA research lists of employees; general campaign staff; Republican senators & governors.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Speeches (Box 28, Folder 259)
    Excerpts of remarks by NAR; NAR statements & addresses.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Statement, March 21, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 260)
    NAR declares he is not a candidate for the Republican Party Presidential nomination.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Statement, April 30, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 261)
    NAR declares he is running for the Republican Party Presidential nomination.
  - 1968 Presidential Campaign - Winthrop Rockefeller Letters (Box 28, Folder 262)
    Correspondence with Winthrop Rockefeller from citizens asking him to urge his brother to run for president or to seek the nomination himself.
- New York State Gubernatorial Campaigns, 1958-1970; 3; 33 Document Box(es)
  Subseries 3 is arranged chronologically by campaign, and thereunder alphabetically by subject.
  The majority of this material pertains to the initial campaign in 1958 (82%), with the remaining material distributed between the 1962 (11%), 1966 (6%), and 1970 (1%) campaigns. The 1958 portion begins with three large files of letters to Rockefeller congratulating him upon his nomination and subsequent election as Governor of New York or inquiring about his stand on particular issues. These files include Rockefeller's replies and are arranged alphabetically by correspondent. The remainder of the 1958 material, as with the successive campaign files, consists of alphabetically arranged subject files.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (A-Al) (Box 29, Folder 263)
    After being nominated and then elected as Governor of New York, Rockefeller received many letters of congratulations as well as letters asking for his position or input on certain issues concerning the state or the nation.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Alm-Ax) (Box 29, Folder 264)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ba) (Box 29, Folder 0265A)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ba) (Box 29, Folder 0265B)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Be) (Box 29, Folder 0266A)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Be) (Box 29, Folder 0266B)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Bi-Bo) (Box 29, Folder 267)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Br) (Box 29, Folder 268)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Bu) (Box 29, Folder 269)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ca) (Box 29, Folder 270)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ce-Cl) (Box 29, Folder 271)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Co) (Box 29, Folder 272)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Cr-Cu) (Box 29, Folder 273)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Da-Dei) (Box 30, Folder 274)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Dej-Dew) (Box 30, Folder 275)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Di-Dy) (Box 30, Folder 276)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (E) (Box 30, Folder 277)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Fa-Fir) (Box 30, Folder 278)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Fis-Fo) (Box 30, Folder 279)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Fr-Fu) (Box 30, Folder 280)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ga-Gi) (Box 30, Folder 281)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Gl-Go) (Box 30, Folder 282)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Gra-Gre) (Box 30, Folder 283)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Gri-Gut) (Box 30, Folder 284)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ha-Han) (Box 30, Folder 285)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Har-Hay) (Box 30, Folder 286)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (He-Hi) (Box 31, Folder 287)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ho-Hy) (Box 31, Folder 288)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (I-J) (Box 31, Folder 289)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ka-Ken) (Box 31, Folder 290)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Keo-Kn) (Box 31, Folder 291)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ko-Ky) (Box 31, Folder 292)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (La) (Box 31, Folder 293)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Le) (Box 31, Folder 294)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ll-Ly) (Box 31, Folder 295)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ma-Man) (Box 31, Folder 296)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Mar) (Box 31, Folder 297)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Mas) (Box 31, Folder 298)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Mc) (Box 32, Folder 299)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Me) (Box 32, Folder 300)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Mi) (Box 32, Folder 301)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Mo-Mor) (Box 32, Folder 302)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Mos-My) (Box 32, Folder 303)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Na-Ni) (Box 32, Folder 304)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (No-Nu) (Box 32, Folder 305)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (O-Or) (Box 32, Folder 306)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Os-Oz) (Box 32, Folder 307)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Pa-Pe) (Box 32, Folder 308)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Pf-Po) (Box 32, Folder 309)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Pr-Py) (Box 32, Folder 310)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Q) (Box 32, Folder 311)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ra-Re) (Box 32, Folder 312)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Rho-Riz) (Box 32, Folder 313)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Roa-Roe) (Box 32, Folder 314)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Rog-Roz) (Box 33, Folder 315)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ru-Ry) (Box 33, Folder 316)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Sa) (Box 33, Folder 317)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Sc) (Box 33, Folder 318)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Se) (Box 33, Folder 319)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Sh) (Box 33, Folder 320)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Si-Sm) (Box 33, Folder 321)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Smith) (Box 33, Folder 322)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Sn-Sp) (Box 33, Folder 323)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Sta-Ste) (Box 33, Folder 324)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Sti-Stu) (Box 33, Folder 325)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Su-Sy) (Box 33, Folder 326)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Ta-Ti) (Box 33, Folder 327)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (To-Ty) (Box 33, Folder 328)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (U) (Box 34, Folder 329)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (V) (Box 34, Folder 330)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (W) (Box 34, Folder 331)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (We) (Box 34, Folder 332)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Wh-Wil) (Box 34, Folder 333)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (Win-Wy) (Box 34, Folder 334)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - General Correspondence (X-Z) (Box 34, Folder 335)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged - Sample of Form Letters Sent in Reply to Congratulatory Letters (Box 34, Folder 336)
    Letters of congratulation which were replied by form letter. Only the incoming correspondence was retained.
    General note
    Letters of support and congratulations following NAR's nomination and subsequent election as Governor of New York, and solicitations of his opinion on state and national issues.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (A) (Box 34, Folder 337)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Ba-Bl) (Box 34, Folder 338)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Bo) (Box 34, Folder 339)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (C) (Box 34, Folder 340)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (D) (Box 34, Folder 341)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (E) (Box 35, Folder 342)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (F) (Box 35, Folder 343)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (G) (Box 35, Folder 344)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Ha-Hi) (Box 35, Folder 345)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Ho) (Box 35, Folder 346)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (I-J) (Box 35, Folder 347)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (K) (Box 35, Folder 348)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (La-Lh) (Box 35, Folder 349)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Li) (Box 35, Folder 350)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Ma) (Box 35, Folder 351)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Mc-Mil) (Box 35, Folder 352)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Min) (Box 35, Folder 353)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (N-O) (Box 35, Folder 354)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (P) (Box 35, Folder 355)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Q) (Box 35, Folder 356)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Ra-Ri) (Box 35, Folder 357)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Ro) (Box 35, Folder 358)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Sa-Si) (Box 36, Folder 359)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Sk-Sz) (Box 36, Folder 360)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (T) (Box 36, Folder 361)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (U-V) (Box 36, Folder 362)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (W) (Box 36, Folder 363)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (X-Z) (Box 36, Folder 364)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Form Acknowledged (Anonymous) (Box 36, Folder 365)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (A) (Box 36, Folder 366)
    Letters of congratulation replied to with individually written letters. Copies of most replies are attached.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (B) (Box 36, Folder 367)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (C) (Box 36, Folder 368)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (D-F) (Box 36, Folder 369)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (G-I) (Box 36, Folder 370)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (J-L) (Box 36, Folder 371)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (M) (Box 36, Folder 372)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (N-Q) (Box 36, Folder 373)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (R) (Box 36, Folder 374)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (S) (Box 36, Folder 375)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (T-V) (Box 36, Folder 376)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (W) (Box 37, Folder 377)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Individual Letters (X-Z) (Box 37, Folder 378)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Congratulatory Letters, Nomination (A-C) (Box 37, Folder 379)
    Letters of congratulation and support upon receiving the Republican gubernatorial nomination. Copies of most replies are attached.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Congratulatory Letters, Nomination (D-J) (Box 37, Folder 380)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Congratulatory Letters, Nomination (K-P) (Box 37, Folder 381)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Congratulatory Letters - Congratulatory Letters, Nomination (Q-Z) (Box 37, Folder 382)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Allocations and Expenditures (Box 38, Folder 383)
    Chart for 1958 campaign.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Applicants (Box 38, Folder 384)
    Letters of individuals seeking positions with the campaign or in administration.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Applicants (Box 38, Folder 385)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Applicants (Box 38, Folder 386)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Amper, Richard (Box 38, Folder 387)
    Miscellaneous correspondence & memos.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Biographical Information (Box 38, Folder 388)
    Summary of state & federal roles of NAR; complete profile; "A Man Who Gets Things Done" 10/14/58; "Why I Want to Be Governor"; "Good Neighbors Make Good Partners"; "Nelson Rockefeller and the World of Art"; Summary of programs proposed by NAR as candidate for governor.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Biographical Information (Box 38, Folder 389)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Budget (Box 38, Folder 390)
    Rockefeller for Governor budget through August 31, 1958.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Burton, John E. (Box 38, Folder 391)
    Bio; memos re court reorganization, judicial reform, campaign preparations.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Articles (Box 38, Folder 392)
    Related Archival Materials note
    See also Box 81.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Costs Inquiries (Box 38, Folder 393)
    Public requests for information on campaign costs & other related inquiries.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Materials (Box 39, Folder 394)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Materials, Buttons and Stickers (Box 39, Folder 395)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Materials, Services Offered (Box 39, Folder 396)
    Informational literature from companies that provide campaign materials.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Publications - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating (Box 39, Folder 397)
    Mailers, pamphlets, form letters.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Publications - Democrats for Rockefeller (Box 39, Folder 398)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Publications - [Rockefeller for Governor] Headquarters Publications (Box 39, Folder 399)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Publications - "Meet Nelson Rockefeller" (Box 40, Folder 400)
    Several copies of booklet published for the campaign.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Publications - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 401)
    Literature from small organizations supporting NAR.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Campaign Publications - Republican State Committee (Box 40, Folder 402)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Eisenhower-Nixon (Box 40, Folder 403)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Contributions, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 404)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 405)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Final Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 406)
    Various reports, including financial summaries for the organization.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Form Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 407)
    Samples of form letters sent out on NAR's behalf.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - General, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 408)
    Correspondence and memoranda of the organization.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Real Estate, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 409)
    Addresses of store fronts & donors who agreed to place campaign literature in their storefronts.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Statement of Expenditures, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 410)
    Political expenditures for gubernatorial & senatorial candidates; statement of resources, receipts & disbursements.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Report, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 411)
    Black (Negro) voting activity in NYC.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Thank You Letters, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 412)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Volunteers, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 413)
    Letters of thanks sent to campaign workers.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Volunteers, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 414)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Volunteer Cards, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 415)
    Staff lists containing vital information for contacting the volunteer.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - Women's Division Final Report, 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 416)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating - "Women's Kit", 1958-1959 (Box 41, Folder 417)
    Campaign kit.
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Clippings (Box 41, Folder 418)
  - 1958 Gubernatorial Campaign - Subject Files - Clippings (Box 41, Folder 419)